firstthings.com 2018-12-27

# Terms & Conditions | First Things

First Things is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide us when using our website. This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit FirstThings.com.

### Information We Collect

When you use certain features of this site, we may collect personal information from you that may include your name, address and e-mail address. Also, we automatically collect non-personal information from you, such as “Internet Protocol (IP) addresses” and “cookies”. An IP address is a numeric address assigned to your computer. It is not linked to any personally identifiable information, so your name remains anonymous. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computerâ€™s hard drive. Cookies allow the website to store and reference specific types of information while you are visiting a site. Information collected is used on an aggregate basis only; for example, to tell us how visitors commonly use and navigate this site.

### How We Use Information That is Collected

We may use personal information in the following ways:

To send e-mail acknowledgements of subscription order or correspondence conducted on the website. To send you e-mail renewal notices. To enhance existing features or develop new features, products, and services. To provide First Things advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our websiteâ€™s user base and usage patterns. To process subscriptions, to verify your credit card data, and to send you a receipt.

### Security

Our website employ security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use a secure server to protect the security of your online transactions. Your information is transmitted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard for sending encrypted information. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

### Other

When you use [FirstThings.com](http://www.firstthings.com/), you consent to our collection and use of the personal information you provide. First Things does not disclose personally identifying information about its users to others without their consent. Please note that if at any time First Things is required by law or a legal process to release individual or organizational information, we must cooperate fully.

### Policy Modifications

Our privacy policy may change, so please check back from time to time.

### Comments and Questions

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, you may contact us at [ft@firstthings.com](mailto:ft@firstthings.com) or by regular mail at: 

First Things  
35 East 21st Street, 6th floor  
New York, New York 10010.
